dbid	id	Headline	Note_Entry	Notes_Log
33554433	Prod00000001	S2 - Not commenting closure of loops		 ==== State: Resolved by: junnykins on 14 May 2013 16:14:44 ====  Comments added at the end of the loop braces to indicate where...
33554434	Prod00000002	S2 - Un-needed library		
33554435	Prod00000003	S4 - Un-needed continue		
33554436	Prod00000004	S2 - Un-needed Return		
33554437	Prod00000005	S6 - Long call to method, not needed		
33554438	Prod00000006	D1 - Overly excessive Commenting of code.	Remove the excessive comments to make the code easier to read.	 ==== State: Closed by: junnykins on 14 May 2013 16:16:16 ====  Remove the excessive comments to make the code easier to read. 
33554439	Prod00000007	D1 - Overly excessive Commenting of code.	Remove the excessive comments to make the code easier to read.	 ==== State: Closed by: junnykins on 14 May 2013 16:16:30 ====  Remove the excessive comments to make the code easier to read. 
33554440	Prod00000008	D1 - Overly excessive Commenting of code.	Remove the excessive comments to make the code easier to read.	 ==== State: Closed by: junnykins on 14 May 2013 16:16:39 ====  Remove the excessive comments to make the code easier to read. 
33554441	Prod00000009	D1 - Overly excessive Commenting of code.	Remove the excessive comments to make the code easier to read.	 ==== State: Closed by: junnykins on 14 May 2013 16:16:49 ====  Remove the excessive comments to make the code easier to read. 
33554442	Prod00000010	D1 - Overly excessive Commenting of code.	Remove the excessive comments to make the code easier to read.	 ==== State: Closed by: junnykins on 14 May 2013 16:17:17 ====  Remove the excessive comments to make the code easier to read. 
33554443	Prod00000011	D1 - Overly excessive Commenting of code.	Remove the excessive comments to make the code easier to read.	 ==== State: Closed by: junnykins on 14 May 2013 16:17:24 ====  Remove the excessive comments to make the code easier to read. 
33554444	Prod00000012	D1 - Overly excessive Commenting of code.	Remove the excessive comments to make the code easier to read.	 ==== State: Closed by: junnykins on 14 May 2013 16:17:34 ====  Remove the excessive comments to make the code easier to read. 
33554445	Prod00000013	D1 - Overly excessive Commenting of code.	Remove the excessive comments to make the code easier to read.	 ==== State: Closed by: junnykins on 14 May 2013 16:17:46 ====  Remove the excessive comments to make the code easier to read. 
33554446	Prod00000014	V1 - Badly named variable		
33554447	Prod00000015	V1 - Badly named variable		
33554448	Prod00000016	V1 - Badly named Variable		
33554449	Prod00000017	L3 - No default Else case	Consider adding a default else case to the if loop.	 ==== State: Closed by: gunnarviking on 14 May 2013 16:19:38 ====  Consider adding a default else case to the if loop. 
33554450	Prod00000018	L4 - No default case		
33554451	Prod00000019	S1 - Implements too many numbers	Removing the final print to the interface could remove the issue with the excessive numbers being printed.   Alternatively, the ...	 ==== State: Closed by: gunnarviking on 14 May 2013 16:21:32 ====  Removing the final print to the interface could remove the is...
33554452	Prod00000020	S4 - error with if loop		 ==== State: Closed by: gunnarviking on 14 May 2013 16:22:44 ====  The if loop could be closed, as this part of the code could b...
33554453	Prod00000021	L7 - Code in loop could be outside	Code could be re-written to be outside of this loop, the loop may not be needed at all and could speed up the application.	 ==== State: Closed by: gunnarviking on 14 May 2013 16:23:57 ====  Code could be re-written to be outside of this loop, the loop...
33554454	Prod00000022	S4 - If loop		
33554457	Prod00000025	V1		 ==== State: Resolved by: gunnarviking on 16 May 2013 11:45:35 ====  Resolved as per first note.  ==== State: Closed by: gunnarv...
33554458	Prod00000026	V1	Change the variable name so that it better reflects what it's use is, and so it is less ambiguous.	 ==== State: Closed by: gunnarviking on 16 May 2013 11:45:23 ====  Change the variable name so that it better reflects what it's...
33554459	Prod00000027	V1	Change the variable name to be less ambiguous and a better description of what it is or what it is holding.	 ==== State: Closed by: gunnarviking on 16 May 2013 11:45:18 ====  Change the variable name to be less ambiguous and a better de...
33554460	Prod00000028	L7		
33554461	Prod00000029	S4	The continue isn't really needed and could be removed.	 ==== State: Closed by: junnykins on 16 May 2013 11:29:43 ====  The continue isn't really needed and could be removed. 
33554462	Prod00000030	S2		
33554464	Prod00000032	S1		
33554465	Prod00000033	S6		
33554466	Prod00000034	S2	You could remove the return as the method it belongs too is never really called, it would require the return type of the method ...	 ==== State: Closed by: junnykins on 16 May 2013 11:30:36 ====  You could remove the return as the method it belongs too is neve...
33554467	Prod00000035	D1		
33554468	Prod00000036	D1		
33554469	Prod00000037	D1		
33554470	Prod00000038	D1		
33554471	Prod00000039	D1		
33554472	Prod00000040	D1		
33554473	Prod00000041	L3		
33554474	Prod00000042	S2 - Doesn't compute negative Numbers	The application cannot handle negative numbers, perhaps an error message and therefore a catch for negative numbers would be goo...	 ==== State: Closed by: junnykins on 16 May 2013 11:31:36 ====  The application cannot handle negative numbers, perhaps an error...
33554475	Prod00000043	S2 - Overflow when numbers too high	The int holding the value of the sequence overflows with higher numbers.  Try using a larger int or restrict the maximum values ...	 ==== State: Closed by: junnykins on 16 May 2013 11:32:19 ====  The int holding the value of the sequence overflows with higher ...
33554476	Prod00000044	S2 - Overflow of ints		
33554477	Prod00000045	S2 - Ambigious, unhelpful error message	Change the error messages and add more so that they are better and more descriptive of what the actual problem is.  There should...	 ==== State: Closed by: junnykins on 16 May 2013 11:34:09 ====  Change the error messages and add more so that they are better a...
33554478	Prod00000046	S2 - Error message differentiation	Add new error messages so that they are more helpful to indentify what the user has done incorrectly	 ==== State: Closed by: junnykins on 16 May 2013 11:35:14 ====  Add new error messages so that they are more helpful to indentif...
33554479	Prod00000047	S2 - Application failes to calculate numbers too large	Make it so that the application can handle large numbers, or provide the means to prevent them from being entered.	 ==== State: Closed by: gunnarviking on 16 May 2013 11:40:21 ====  Make it so that the application can handle large numbers, or ...
33554480	Prod00000048	S2 - Error message from large numbers is poorly written	Make a new error message for large numbers or update the current message to dynamically show what caused the error message	 ==== State: Closed by: gunnarviking on 16 May 2013 11:40:43 ====  Make a new error message for large numbers or update the curr...
33554481	Prod00000049	S2 - Screen doesn't resize elements when window is enlarged.	Make it so that the elements resize when the box of the application is dragged, or prevent resizing of the screen altogether	 ==== State: Closed by: gunnarviking on 16 May 2013 11:41:14 ====  Make it so that the elements resize when the box of the appli...
33554482	Prod00000050	V1 - Poorly Named Variable	Rename variable to something more readable and less ambiguous, Better related to its function and use.	 ==== State: Closed by: gunnarviking on 16 May 2013 11:46:41 ====  Rename variable to something more readable and less ambiguous...
33554483	Prod00000051	V1 - Line 48 Poorly named variable name.	Rename variable to something more readable and less ambiguous, Better related to its function and use.	 ==== State: Closed by: gunnarviking on 16 May 2013 11:46:47 ====  Rename variable to something more readable and less ambiguous...
33554484	Prod00000052	V1 - Line 52 Poorly named variable name.	Rename variable to something more readable and less ambiguous, Better related to its function and use.	 ==== State: Closed by: gunnarviking on 16 May 2013 11:47:24 ====  Rename variable to something more readable and less ambiguous...
33554485	Prod00000053	V1 - Line 52 Poorly named variable name.	Rename variable to something more readable and less ambiguous, Better related to its function and use.	 ==== State: Closed by: gunnarviking on 16 May 2013 11:47:29 ====  Rename variable to something more readable and less ambiguous...
33554486	Prod00000054	V1 - Line 55 Poorly named variable name.	Rename variable to something more readable and less ambiguous, Better related to its function and use.	 ==== State: Closed by: gunnarviking on 16 May 2013 11:47:30 ====  Rename variable to something more readable and less ambiguous...
33554487	Prod00000055	V1 - Line 55 Poorly named variable name.	Rename variable to something more readable and less ambiguous, Better related to its function and use.	 ==== State: Closed by: gunnarviking on 16 May 2013 11:47:30 ====  Rename variable to something more readable and less ambiguous...
